[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Hurry up!
On my way!
Let's go.
Go take a look.
See?
Look! They're going upstream!
Aren't they going backwards?
Look!
Over there!
Jialiang!
Jiashu!
The immortal children descend.
Against the current, the corpses go.
Jialiang!
Brother.
Stepmother?
Your father is dead.
Your younger brother and sister
are also dead.
No...
Feiyan...
Feiyan.
I need to get an explanation from her.
Scam!
The whole thing is a scam!
Chengming.
Feiyan!
Scam...
Feiyan...
This is a scam!
Feiyan.
This is all a scam!
Jiang Feiyan!
The whole thing is a scam!
You are a jinx.
You got
the whole family killed.
What took you so long?
[A Prophet]
[Episode 1]
[Pangzhou]
Master Hu.
[Hu Guangyuan, Tianxiang Sect]
Who are you, gentleman?
"The founder left 3 treasures.
All disciples got real inheritance."
"Qian harmonizes with Kun, with Li and Kan in balance.
[Du Gui, Tianxiang Sect]
Our fame spreads across every land."
"Zhen, Xun, Gen, and Dui create the wind.
We gather from all corners to make our mark."
You got
all the passwords right.
I am Mu Zilian's 33rd-generation disciple,
Lyu Ruhui.
Greetings, Master Hu.
Good.
Come with us.
[Yaxin Grand Hotel]
The place you arranged is really fancy, Master Hu.
This is a big job.
I can't risk anything going wrong.
So,
sorry for the rough journey.
It's our first time meeting,
but I've heard
a lot about you in Pujiang.
Master Hu,
you can ask me to do anything.
I'm at your command.
Master,
the room is ready.
Okay.
This is Du Gui.
He works for me.
In terms of seniority,
you should call him senior.
Senior Gui.
Gui,
take Ruhui to the room to freshen up.
You're in room 203.
Okay.
See you.
[Eight hours ago]
What took you so long?
Once we reach Pangzhou,
Ruhui,
are you going to do some big business?
No rush.
Once we reach Pangzhou,
I'll first show you around,
find a woman to get rid of the bad luck,
and then get down to business.
There's plenty of time.
Your Tianxiang Sect is amazing.
Ruhui,
do you earn a lot of gold bars
from every deal?
[Lyu Ruhui, Tianxiang Sect]
Remember,
everyone in the Tianxiang Sect
boasts the talent
of a chancellor.
Do you know
what this is?
Only
the Batou
can have this.
What is "Batou"?
A leader.
Looks like I made the right choice following you!
During the trip to Pangzhou,
you must keep your head clear.
When I tell you to strike,
be quick about it.
Ruhui,
didn't you tell me before that
the Tianxiang Sect only tricks people
but never kills them?
Rules were set by our ancestors.
If we never kill,
the pittance we make is barely enough to get by.
You're right.
Chengming,
be careful.
It's indeed not enough for me.
This is just the beginning.
I won't let a single one
of the Tianxiang Sect escape.
[Recorded by Lyu Ruhai]
[Huangsha]
Senior Gui,
I've shaved.
Just in case you didn't
shave it clean enough,
let me shave it for you again.
Where did you come from?
Pujiang.
Which station did you get on the train at?
Fanhuangdu Station.
Why are there 2 tickets?
Miss Lyu from Pujiang
insisted on eloping with me.
She bought the tickets.
Where is she then?
If I brought every girl who wanted
to elope with me,
how could I work for you, Senior Gui?
Listen,
I despise you pretty swindlers
the most, you know?
You gigolos
elope with women and swindle them.
What skills do you even have?
Senior Gui,
this actually requires some skills.
The Philippine cigar—
not as good as Cuban ones.
I'll just make do with it.
Made in Burgundy.
You really spent a lot.
However,
this short, wide glass with a narrow rim is called a cognac glass.
It's meant for brandy.
So it's a bit unconventional.
Interesting.
Fine feathers make
fine birds.
Go pick an outfit.
There's a phone in the room.
Call me
if you need anything.
Senior Gui,
I know you don't like me,
but we still have to get along in the future.
How about this?
I'll treat you to dinner.
Let's
bury the hatchet.
Save it.
You should use that time
to memorize the stuff.
Also,
you're not leaving here
until you've memorized it properly,
understand?
No way.
I've been holding back all the way.
I need to go walk around first.
Brat,
listen.
Don't get too big for your britches,
understand?
Gigolos like you are
a dime a dozen in our Tianxiang Sect.
If you screw things up,
I'll kill you
before my master even has to give an order.
We don't have much time left.
[Chen Qingying]
We've got only one night.
You must memorize every single word
on this.
Whether this plan succeeds or not
all depends on you.
Congratulations, President Chen!
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you all for coming to show your support.
Thank you, thank you so much.
President Chen!
Director Zhao!
President Chen.
Congratulations
on opening your new store!
I'm just running a small business.
I'll still need your support, Director Zhao.
If yours is a small business,
then no one in Pangzhou City would dare to do business.
Where is Qingying?
She was here just now.
[Chen's Gold Shop]
Congratulations, Daddy.
Qingying!
Hi, Mr. Zhao.
I'll talk to you later, Mr. Zhao.
Okay.
Daddy.
Get changed and throw this suit away right now.
A female university graduate
from Cambridge hangs out
with these low-class people every day.
How inappropriate!
Stop talking about upper class and lower class all the time.
Abraham Lincoln said,
"All men are created equal."
If you were a boy, I wouldn't even bother with you.
But you are my only daughter.
If you keep this up,
who's ever going to marry you?
Daddy,
do you really want me to get married?
What nonsense are you talking about?
A grown-up girl
has to get married, of course.
If I get married,
our gold shops,
pawnshops,
and restaurants
will all belong to someone else.
That's why I can only take in a live-in son-in-law,
and every son you have must take the Chen family name!
Okay!
I'll go find one for you right now.
Where are you going?
Come back here!
I'm going to return the suit.
Mr. Lin,
here is the newspaper you ordered.
Thank you.
[Lin Shengxiang arrived in Suicheng yesterday.]
Okay, I got it.
Okay.
That's it.
Master.
What's wrong?
I mean, look at you.
Why are your looks so disappointing?
If you were even a bit decent-looking,
I wouldn't have had to get someone here from Pujiang.
Thankfully,
he looks quite quick-witted.
Well, it's not my fault how I look.
Then whose fault is it?
Why didn't you take after your mother?
Fine, fine.
Just blame it on my disappointing looks.
You said he's quick-witted.
But I don't think so.
I think this brat
is a bit fishy.
He gave all the right passwords.
The token is also real.
But I still can't feel at ease.
How about this?
I'll send them a telegram
to confirm, just to be safe.
Don't bother.
After we wrap up this job,
he'll be gone.
Gone?
Isn't he your junior's disciple?
Your looks are disappointing,
so is your brain.
"Different branches, different ties."
Haven't you heard of this saying?
Isn't it good to have one less person to share the money with?
Master,
you are really wicked.
Master Hu.
Long time no see.
Long time no see,
Mr. Lin.
Welcome to Pangzhou.
Alright,
everything is ready.
Go with your senior.
Okay.
Let's go.
What's wrong with your eyes?
Keep a close eye on him!
What did I do to deserve this?
Every Wednesday night,
Miss Chen comes to this bar
and orders a special brandy as well as a portion of fried fish,
because her favorite band
only performs on Wednesday nights.
The band finishes their performance at 9 PM.
Miss Chen always comes secretly
behind her father's back.
She comes and goes by a rickshaw.
From here to her house,
she has to pass through 3 blocks.
Our men will lie in ambush on Shamo Street in advance
and act immediately once we spot her.
Your mission this time
is to rescue Chen Qingying
from our men.
You'll be doing great.
As the son of a rich businessman in San Francisco
and her savior,
you can take
this first step easily.
Come on.
Saving the damsel in distress—
how cliché.
What do you mean?
Just say your lines!
Where are you going?
Hello.
Someone hired me for 100 silver dollars a day
to make you fall for me.
This opening line
is new to me.
It's real.
And
I took the job.
Miss Chen,
do you need help?
One special brandy
and one fried fish.
Okay.
Two brandies.
Just a moment.
So how do you plan to court me?
I don't know.
We could
first go shopping,
see an opera,
watch a movie,
and then
meet your parents.
That's too slow.
Why not just meet my parents directly?
That works, too.
My family has a lot of rules.
You can only be my matrilocal husband.
No problem.
We can have 2 children.
The first one takes your surname,
and the second one takes mine.
No way.
They must both take my surname.
I suppose I can live with that.
You're quite interesting.
If I had asked you to leave just now,
you wouldn't have had the chance to say these, huh?
I would've had the chance.
We'd hire a few men to ambush you on the way.
Once they get you under control,
I'd swoop in
and take them all down.
After that,
you'd believe
whatever I say.
Saving the damsel in distress?
What a cliché.
It is a bit of a cliché.
However,
there are always some fools who will buy it.
Let me tell you a story.
Listen, you need to understand your father.
He's getting old.
Of course, he wants you to inherit the family business,
right?
I studied architecture abroad, not business.
I've always looked up to Mr. Liang as my role model.
Chinese learning as the base,
Western learning for application.
I hope my life...
Yes,
you studied abroad and returned
with a degree in architecture.
Right?
This and inheriting
your family's silk business
don't conflict at all.
They don't conflict? How?
Do you know how many people
envy you for having such a father?
-Bravo! -Bravo!
♪ There is a fiery woman in the brothel ♪
-Nice! -Bravo!
Sir.
Did you get someone else
to play Liang Hongyu?
Yes.
The previous one's voice changed.
This is the new performer.
♪ She sees one man off only to welcome another every day ♪
Her stage name is Feiyan.
Her figure and voice are both excellent.
The manager let her fill in for a couple of shows.
When this show is over,
send 2 flower baskets to the backstage for me.
Don't mention my name.
Got it.
Please enjoy it, sirs.
-Bravo! -Bravo!
Go back!
What do you want?
Help!
We are a bit cash-strapped.
We just want to borrow some money from you.
If you don't have any,
then we'll borrow something else.
What are you doing here?
It's none of your business.
Get lost!
Aren't you the one who played Liang Hongyu?
If she is "Liang Hongyu,"
then you must be "Han Shizhong."
You want to marry this bitch
and let her sing for you in bed every day,
right?
What a pity.
Before the wedding,
I have to hold a funeral for you first.
Boss,
boss,
we are all making a living.
Sorry for the offense.
Run! Run quickly!
Are you okay?
This is fake.
A toy I bought for my younger brother.
Then please
put it away.
By the way,
did you receive the flower baskets?
I sent them.
So were those hooligans
really hired by that man?
Maybe they were
hired by that woman.
A woman
had someone harass her.
What if the man didn't show up and save her?
Wouldn't she end up in a bind?
If this woman had
investigated this man thoroughly beforehand,
there would've been no "what if."
What happened next?
Next...
Happy birthday.
You...
How did you know my birthday?
I have my ways.
This is
the first time someone
made longevity noodles for me.
Because no one has ever
celebrated my birthday since I was little.
Thank you.
My father died an untimely death.
I grew up with my mother.
My mother has been
seriously ill for years.
We've seen many doctors, but none could cure her.
Therefore,
no one could spare a thought for things like this.
What illness does your mother have?
Some of my classmates study Western medicine.
I can have them consult on her case.
It won't help.
I once
ran into an old gentleman surnamed Du.
He told me that
my mother fell ill
all because of me,
and I was a born jinx, bringing misfortune
to my parents, relatives, friends,
and my devoted lover.
In a nutshell,
everyone who treats me well
will end up
dead because of me.
That's utter nonsense.
It's all true.
Moreover,
Mr. Du also told me that
the only way to get rid of this bad luck
was to remain unmarried for life
and work in the lowest professions—
I should either be a lowly performer
or...
Or be a whore.
Where is that old guy?
I'll go find him right now!
Mr. Du wanders all over the country.
You can't find him.
But
since I started trying this method,
my mother's indeed been
taking a turn for the better.
So this really works.
Don't believe him.
These fortune tellers all talk nonsense.
Why should performers who play miserable people
be considered the lowliest?
I actually think
they've got real backbone.
Well,
take me to your mother,
and I'll take her to see a doctor.
How about that?
It's all superstition.
Birth, aging, illness, and death
are part of the natural order.
Those who describe a pretty woman as the source of disaster
are mostly
miserable and pathetic themselves
and can't stand seeing others do well.
Everyone
has something they believe in.
It could be gods or Buddhas,
money or power.
What about you?
What do you believe in?
I believe in myself.
That's nice.
So, were those two people
going to fall in love next?
It's getting late.
Your parents must be worried about you.
It's this late now?
I got so caught up in your story that I lost track of time.
Let me escort you home.
Don't bother.
My lady.
You're quite a good storyteller.
I'll tell you more if there's a chance.
You came back so late again.
As a young lady,
you go to bars every night
and come back so late.
If anything happens to you,
how will you ever get married then?
Come on.
What could possibly happen to me?
You reek of alcohol!
Who were you drinking with tonight?
With him.
Lin Shengxiang, the son of a leader in the overseas Chinese community?
I can stab you to death. Do you believe it?
Master,
you told me to keep a close eye on him.
I watched him like a hawk.
But this bastard
didn't stick to the script at all!
Ouch! It Hurts!
Gui.
Having you around
will take years off my life.
What?
Answer me.
Why did you act on your own?
If I had done what you told me to do,
the whole plan would be screwed up.
Do you really think
a rich heiress wouldn't have bodyguards with her
when she goes to a bar at night?
Do you know her that well?
I sleep with that book in my arms every night!
No one knows her better than me!
Let go.
Get up.
This brat
simply got dumb luck.
He has no brains.
That woman is even crazier than him!
He has more brains than you.
Since the very first day you started working for me,
I've told you
to strike fast and con patiently.
He hit the mark in the first place.
No matter how he cons Chen Qingying afterwards,
she won't suspect him anymore.
Kid,
you did well this time.
However,
if you dare to act
without permission again,
I'll skin you alive.
Master,
our plan is already ruined now.
What should we do next?
You can't set up a chance encounter
for them again, right?
Don't worry about that.
She will
definitely contact me in 3 days.
Coming.
Hi.
Miss Chen?
What brings you here?
What?
Am I not welcome here?
Coming to see me so openly, aren't you afraid
someone will see us?
Are you afraid?
Why would I be?
I'm hired for 100 silver dollars a day.
How about this?
Give me half your remuneration,
and I promise I won't tell anyone.
You can have it all.
What's the plan?
Are we going shopping or going to the opera today?
Didn't I tell you?
We're going to meet my parents directly.
Let's go.
Come home with me.
Mr. Lin,
is our food to your liking?
Hometown food made
in your hometown tastes the best.
I couldn't get the same flavor where I used to live.
It always felt like something was missing.
Qingying felt the same as you.
Back when she was studying in England,
she always missed our homemade food
and craved this taste.
Mr. Lin,
which school did you attend in America?
MIT.
Pardon?
That's a good school.
Pretty good.
What are you planning to do this time you're back?
To be honest with you,
I'm planning to buy a tin mine.
For mining?
The mining business is
pretty complicated.
You are new here.
If you run into any difficulties,
just feel free to tell me.
I will do whatever I can to help you.
Thank you, sir.
But my father told me
to find
a remarkable feng shui master—
Mr. Song,
Song Tiezui—
and follow his advice on buying the mine.
I've never heard of the need for a master
when it comes to buying a mine.
Yeah,
Shengxiang.
As one of the young generation,
do you also believe in feng shui?
My father said that
he asked this master
to change his fate,
and that was how he came to have today's fortune.
"Song Tiezui"?
How come I've never heard
of such a person in Pangzhou before?
Mr. Song is
incredibly elusive.
I only came here because I heard he showed up
in Pangzhou.
Good.
By the way,
Shengxiang,
just let Qingying show you
around Pangzhou for the next couple of days.
All the prominent figures here
are my friends.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask them.
Then I'll take you up on that, sir.
Good.
Come on.
Let's eat up.
Okay.
Your mother?
I just said that in the heat of the moment.
Chen Jiarong asked me
why I came to Pangzhou alone without anyone to look after me.
I...
I just blurted out without thinking
that my mom was coming tomorrow.
Never thought that Miss Chen
would offer to play host
and hold a banquet for us on behalf of the Chens.
I was afraid that if I refused,
she and her father would get suspicious.
Wait,
tomorrow?
Where do you expect me
to find one for you in such a short time?
Master Hu, as omnipotent as you are,
it shouldn't be too hard for you to find
an old lady to put on a show with me, right?
Alright, enough, stop massaging.
This is the first
and last time I'll do this.
Let's get this straight first.
It costs money to find someone to do it.
The expense will come out of your pay.
As it should!
Your mother is coming tomorrow?
Why are you only telling me now?
She was traveling in Pujiang
and suddenly asked to visit me.
Probably because
she was bored being alone.
That's a good thing.
Since you're in Pangzhou,
I'll make the arrangements.
How about we
invite your mother for dinner tomorrow?
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
We're already shorthanded in Pangzhou,
and he needs this so urgently.
Good thing the old madam hasn't left.
We can have her fill in temporarily.
This Lyu Ruhui
keeps messing around.
After we wrap up this job,
let's get rid of him immediately
in case he causes more trouble.
♪ Han Shizhong ♪
♪ Fell from power ♪
♪ with his ambition unfulfilled ♪
♪ He ran into... ♪
You must be the young man recommended by Hu Guangyuan.
Have you memorized your lines?
Don't get cold feet
at the last minute
and ruin the show.
It's been so many years.
I missed you so much.
Mother.
[Old Madam Zhu, Tianxiang Sect]
[In the next episode]
Young Master,
Jialiang and Jiashu
are missing.
What?
Jialiang!
Jiashu!
Sir,
you must save them.
I'm willing to give up my family business
and my everything
to renovate the temple
and rebuild the gold-leaf statue
for the Immortal Elder!